#### Contact

ade8943@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/adeogunmokun-2ab27559 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Acute Care Wound Care Patient Advocacy

## Languages

Yoruba

### Certifications

Board Certified by ANCC Adult Psychiatric-Mental Health

Nurse Practitioner (PMHNP-BC)

# Ade Ogunmokun

Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner/PMHNP-BC at Sumo Medical Staffing Richmond, Texas

# Summary

Psychiatry is my love/passion, I couldn't/wouldn't be in any other specialty. Working in mental health enables me bring awareness to the community, of how paramount it is to show compassion, respect and understand mental illness. I also believe it's my moral obligation, to share my knowledge/expertise in psychiatry, with as many people as I possibly can.

# Experience

Sumo Medical Staffing MSN, APN, PMHNP-BC April 2020 - Present (3 months) Utah, United States

Consilium Staffing
MSN,APN,PMHNP-BC
February 2015 - November 2019 (4 years 10 months)
Locums

Providing medication management, comprehensive assessment, planning, developing, and implementing the plan of care. Demonstrating thorough understanding of all requirements and practice standards relating to the prescribing, the administration of medications including compliance with organization policy and procedures, documentation, requirements, and medication education.

PrimeHealth Staffing, LLC MSN,APN,PMHNP-BC May 2015 - October 2015 (6 months) Alpharetta, GA

Meeting with patients to prescribe necessary medications (medication management) that fit treatment plan/goal, Diagnosing Axis I-III, and managing Axis IV-V, as needed. Working as the patient's primary psychiatric provider to achieve psychological stability, with the goal of attaining higher functioning ability.

Starbranch and Associates
MSN,APN,PMHNP-BC
January 2015 - February 2015 (2 months)
United States

Providing medication management, comprehensive assessment, planning, developing, and implementing the plan of care. Demonstrating thorough understanding of all requirements and practice standards relating to the prescribing, the administration of medications including compliance with organization policy and procedures, documentation, requirements, and medication education.

Gulf Coast Medical Center MSN, APN, PMHNP-BC /Clinical Program Manager October 2014 - January 2015 (4 months) Wharton, TX

Manager of the Mental Health Division. In charge of managing entire mental health treatment team. 2nd in command to the Clinical Program Director(Dr. Moin). Establishing the direction that mental health care should go, in regards to my division. Developing programs to implement in our area. Functioning clinically as a Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner by providing initial assessments, history & physicals,follow-ups(progress notes), psychiatric consults, medication management, discharge summary, using the DSM-V to establish the proper diagnosis, implementing the Global Assessment Functioning scale (GAF), establishing Axis I-V and the likes.

Westoaks Hospital
5 years 8 months

Nurse
October 2008 - May 2014 (5 years 8 months)

Charge Nurse

Nurse October 2008 - May 2014 (5 years 8 months) Relief Suprviser, and charge nurse

## Education

University of Cincinnati
MSN, PMHNP, Psychiatric Nurse Practitioner · (2011 - 2013)

University of Houston
BSN, Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2010)

San Jacinto College RN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2006)

San Jacinto College LVN, Practical Nursing, Vocational Nursing and Nursing Assistants · (2002 - 2003)